{
    "id": "2da9919338f34ccba68413684ea824ed",
    "title": "As, Though And Although",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Hot ………………….. it was, we decided to go out.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "as",
                "although",
                "though"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "b9a72fa196744a64a158c9fb180689dc"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………… she was not ready, we went without her.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "As",
                "Though",
                "Although"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "098758775f5343ca89eb7c8451828d1a"
        },
        {
            "question": "Bravely …………………. we fought, we had little chance of winning.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "as",
                "though",
                "although"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "4ce6c9123f604dbd86428f4e17fa3242"
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………. it might seem, she doesn’t like babies.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Though strange",
                "Strange though",
                "Strange although",
                "Although strange"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "dd42f8cfc64e438399a1a992b8fc1be9"
        },
        {
            "question": "I can’t come and spend the weekend with you, ……………….. I would like to.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "as much",
                "much as",
                "although"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "275754e323754e2cb261af62e42a3b66"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………….. I didn’t know anybody at the party, I had a nice time.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Though",
                "Although",
                "As"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "2596070a2ffc4a5d9f6445cb93878d43"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………………… I was tired, I decided to get some rest.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "As",
                "Though",
                "Although"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "eb8e7ae223ac494c90ea9157c7996184"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………………. I was ill for several months, I lost my job.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "As",
                "Though",
                "Although"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "b29a11bf3ad8467dbb63b011b4a7c42d"
        },
        {
            "question": "We decided to go out ……………………. it was a bit late.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "though",
                "although",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "8fae8c90939b430f82ee998006e39c5d"
        },
        {
            "question": "‘Lovely evening.’ ‘Yes. Bit cold, …………………’",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "though",
                "although",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "3e34f32d4ff34e9b8ddaf462d215398a"
        }
    ]
}